Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1921-2017 RL.00052
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Professional Service, 1970s-2015
  - Conferences, Consulting, and Organizations, 1970s-2015; 1
    - Environmental Policy Decisions, 1990 (Box 21)
      Presentation given to Operations Research Symposium for Industrial Affiliates and Corporate Friends at Stanford University
    - EPA Discount Rate, 1982 (Box 49)
      Files related to consulting on EPA use of discount rates
    - EPRI (Electric Power Research Institute), 1982 (Box 49)
      Files related to consulting contract
    - Erling Persson Program, 2012 (Box 21)
    - Esmee Fairbairn Research Center, 1978 (Box 49)
    - ESRC (Economic and Social Research Council), 1986-2012; 2 folders (Box 49)
      Files related to proposal evaluations
    - ESRC: Hahn Review, 1993 (Box 49)
      Files related to reviewing proposal by Frank Hahn
    - European University Institute, 1981-1986 (Box 49)
      Files related to conference travel and presentation
    - FACS Institute for Journalists, 1989 (Box 21)
      Documents related to serving as faculty at summer institute
    - Fair Share, 1975-1976 (Box 49)
      Files related to proposal to revise electric rates in Massachusetts
    - FAT: Milan Meeting, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1981-2001; 2 folders (Box 49)
      Files related to sponsoring organization
    - Fels Center of Government, 1970-1974 (Box 49)
    - Feminist Economics (International Association for Feminist Economics, IAFFE), 1994-1997 (Box 21)
      Documents related to serving on advisory board for Feminist Economics, journal of the International Association for Feminist Economics
    - Fitoussi Fest, 2012-2013 (Box 21)
      Conference in honor of Jean-Paul Fitoussi
    - Florence, 1986 (Box 21)
      Visit to European University Institute in Florence, Italy
    - Florence Bioethical Conference, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Food and Disarmament International, 1981-1987 (Box 49)
    - Food Safety Council, undated (Box 49)
    - Ford Foundation, 1984 (Box 63)
      Files for project proposal "The Future and the Welfare State"
    - France-Stanford Center, 2002-2003 (Box 49)
    - France-Stanford Political Economy Conference, 2003-2004 (Box 21)
    - Freeman-Spogli Institute, 2007 (Box 21)
    - French Economic Measurement, 2008 (Box 21)
      Documents related to conference on Organisation of Work of the Commission on the Measurement of Economic Performance and Social Progress
    - French Proposal, 2001 (Box 63)
      Files related to proposed collaboration between Stanford and France
    - FRESH, 2009-2012 (Box 21)
      Documents related to workshop on medical education
    - Friedman Panel, 1987 (Box 21)
      Accepting invitation to panel celebrating Milton Friedman's birthday
    - Fuchs Symposium, 1995 (Box 21)
      Accepted invitation to conference in honor of Victor Fuchs
    - Fulbright, 2013 (Box 21)
    - Fulbright: Siena, 1995 (Box 21)
    - FUR - Foundations and Applications of Utility, Risk, and Decision Theory, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Gamble Lecture, 1998 (Box 21)
      Files associated with lecture given at University of Massachusetts Amherst
    - Game Theory Congress: Bilbao, 2000 (Box 21)
    - Game Theory Society, 2011 (Box 21)
    - Game Theory vs. General Equilibrium Analysis, 1995 (Box 21)
      Notes for talk at Frank Hahn's 70th birthday
    - Gandhi Institute, 1996-1997 (Box 49)
    - General Equilibrium Conference, 1993 (Box 21)
      Documents for conference celebrating 40th anniversary of general equilibrium hosted by Center for Operations Research and Economics in Belgium
    - Georgia Tech Lecture, 2013 (Box 21)
      College of Computing Distinguished Lecture
    - German Business Congress, 1995 (Box 21)
    - German Trip, 1990 (Box 21)
      Documents about traveling as part of a delegation of scholars to recently reunified Germany
    - Global Health Group, 2014 (Box 21)
    - Gore, Senator Albert, 1990-1991 (Box 49)
      Files related to presentation for meeting
    - Gothenburg, 1998 (Box 21)
      Lecture on social choice and individual choice
    - Graduate Student Talk, 1999 (Box 21)
      Talk on "Information, the Economy, and Economics"
    - Greater Talent Network, Inc., 1988 (Box 21)
      Documents related to speech on the "Multiple Responsibilities of Corporation" given at First International Symposium on Stakeholders
    - Group Decision and Negotiation Journal, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Grunberg Lecture, 1994 (Box 21)
      Lecture on "Economic Transition: Speed and Scope" given at the University of Akron
    - Guggenheim, 1974-1992; 3 folders (Box 49)
      Files related to serving on Board of Trustees and on Committee of Selection
    - Hahn Memorial, 2013 (Box 21)
    - Haldi, 1975 (Box 49)
    - Hamburg Seminar, 1989 (Box 21)
      Accepted invitation to conference on "The Limits of Rationality"
    - Hao Ran Foundation Summer Workshop, 1989-1990 (Box 21)
      Lecture on "Socialist Economic Reform"
    - Harsanyi: Berkeley, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
      Talk on "Ethical Obligations in Business" in honor of John Harsanyi
    - Hart Fest, 2014 (Box 21)
      Invitation to conference in honor of Sergiu Hart
    - Health Economics Research Organization, 1973 (Box 21)
      Invitation to sessions of the Health Economics Research Organization at the ASSA
    - Hebrew University, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 49)
      Files related to serving on external appointment committee
    - Hebrew University of Jerusalem: Center for Rationality, 1998-2012 (Box 21)
      Documents related to annual meetings of Academic Committee
    - Hebrew University: Advisory Committee, 1999 (Box 49)
    - Hebrew University: Mount Scopus, 1998-1999 (Box 49)
    - Heinz Awards, 2005 (Box 49)
    - Heller-Hurwicz Institute, 2010-2011; 2 folders (Box 21)
      Documents for meeting of Advisory Board
    - Heritage of Mankind, 1980-1991 (Box 49)
      Files related to grant proposal
    - Hewlett Foundation, 2008-2013 (Box 63)
      Files for grant-funded project
    - Hewlett Packard, 1983 (Box 49)
      Files related to consulting agreement
    - Hewlett Sustainability Project, 2001-2006 (Box 50)
    - Hicks Conference, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 21)
      Files related to presentation and edited volume celebrating 50th anniversary of "Value and Capital" by Hicks
    - Hillel, 1980-1992 (Box 50)
    - Hitotsubashi-Stanford Conference, 1986-1987 (Box 21)
    - Hong Kong, 1996 (Box 21)
      Declined invitation to speak at University of Hong Kong
    - Hong Kong Lecture, 1993 (Box 21)
      Lecture on "Economic Transition: Speed and Scope" given as 30th Anniversary Distinguished Lecture at Chinese University of Hong Kong
    - Hoover, 1994 (Box 50)
      Correspondence related to declining Senior Fellow appointment at Hoover Institute
    - Hoover: Antitrust Conference, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Hoover: Conference on Economic Transition, 1991 (Box 21)
    - Human Rights and Welfare Economics, 2003 (Box 21)
      Presentation on "Welfare Economics and Childhood"
    - Humboldt State University, 1987 (Box 21)
      Invitation to give Kieval Lecture
    - Hungarian Trip, 1983 (Box 21)
    - Hurwicz Fest, 2007 (Box 21)
      Presentation on "Limited Network Connections and the Distribution of Wages" given at conference in honor of Leo Hurwicz
    - Hypothesis, 1997-2000; 2 folders (Box 21)
      Documents related to "10 Nobels for the Future" talk organized by Hypothesis in Milan, Italy
    - IDDRI (Institute for Sustainable Development and International Relations), 2002-2004 (Box 51)
    - IEA (International Economic Association): Accounts, 1986 (Box 50)
    - IEA: American Economic Association, 1988-1990 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Arrears, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Association Members, 1983-1988 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Booklet, 1984 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Conference, 1984 (Box 21)
    - IEA: Conference - Mexico, 1985 (Box 21)
    - IEA: Congress - Greece Papers, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - IEA: Congress - India, 1984-1991; 4 folders (Box 22)
      Files related to organizing the IEA's eighth World Congress
    - IEA: Congress - Moscow, 1992; 5 folders (Box 23)
      Files related to the IEA's tenth World Congress
    - IEA: Congress - Tunis, 1995 (Box 23)
    - IEA: Congress Addresses, 1986 (Box 21)
    - IEA: Congress Addresses, 1986-1988; 5 folders (Box 22)
    - IEA: Congress Buenos Aires, 1999-2002 (Box 22)
    - IEA: Congress Discussion openers, 1986 (Box 22)
    - IEA: Congress Environment, 1994 (Box 22)
    - IEA: Eighth World Congress, 1985-1986; 24 folders (Box 22)
      Files related to organizing the IEA's eighth World Congress, include sessions 1-17, organizers, papers received, lectures, grants, and the program.
    - IEA: Eighth World Congress submissions, 1986; 8 folders (Box 23)
    - IEA: Congress Travel Grants, 1986 (Box 23)
    - IEA: Council Meeting, 1986-1992; 3 folders (Box 50)
    - IEA: Early Negotiations, 1979-1984; 3 folders (Box 50)
      Files related to planning IEA meetings
    - IEA: East Asia Institution, 1996 (Box 23)
    - IEA: Executive Committee, 1992-1999; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - IEA: Executive Committee Meetings, 1984-1993; 11 folders (Box 50)
    - IEA: Executive Committee Members, 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - IEA: Executive Committee Minutes, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - IEA: Fauvel, Luc Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Financial Accounts, 1984 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Financial Advisory, 1986 (Box 50)
    - IEA: Financial Advisory Committee, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - IEA: Financial Advisory Committee Booklets, 1984 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Fitoussi, Jean-Paul, 1984-1992 (Box 51)
      Correspondence related to IEA business
    - IEA: Forthcoming Conferences, 1983-1987; 3 folders (Box 24)
    - IEA: Future Conferences, 1985-1986 (Box 51)
    - IEA: General Information, 1983-1986 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Hillebrandt, Dr. Patricia M., 1987 (Box 51)
    - IEA: International Social Science Council, 1983-1987; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - IEA: International Center, 1987 (Box 51)
    - IEA: International Sociological Association, 1984 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Israeli Economic Association, 1983-1984 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Meade Conference, 1991 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Michael Kaser, 1986-1990 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 51)
    - IEA: New International Graduate School, 1991 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Newsletter, 2000 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Newsletter, 1981-1991 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Nominating Committee, 1991 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Officers, 1983-1989; 2 folders (Box 51)
    - IEA: Partnership Conference, 1990 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Past President, 1986 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Policy Statement, 1988 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Presidency, 1982 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Proceedings, 1990 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Proceedings, vol. 1, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - IEA: Publications, 1986 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Rationality Conference - Turin, 1993 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Recollections, 1987 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Robinson Obit., 1993 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Secretary, 1983-1989 (Box 51)
    - IEA: SEED, 1991-1994 (Box 51)
      Files related to School of Economics and Economic Development
    - IEA: Sen, Amartya, 1989-1991 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Social Choice Roundtable, 1989-1993 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Social Choice Session, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Staff, 1990 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Stationery, undated (Box 51)
    - IEA: Statutes, 1984-1987 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Suspense - Pending Replies, 1984 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Sylos Labini, Paolo, 1985 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Tokyo Roundtable, 1996 (Box 24)
    - IEA: Trento, 1997 (Box 24)
    - IEA: UNESCO, 1984-1986 (Box 51)
    - IEA: Urquidi, Victor, 1984 (Box 51)
    - IHEA (International Health Economics Association), 1993-1994 (Box 52)
      Files related to Kenneth J. Arrow award selection
    - IMS Health, 2011-2014 (Box 63)
    - Incentives for Global Health, 2011 (Box 24)
    - Income Inequality Conference, 1993 (Box 24)
    - INDECON (Industrial Economics, Inc.), 1997 (Box 50)
      Files related to report on Irish economy
    - India Trip, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
      Files related to travel for IEA's eighth World Congress and other visits made on the same trip
    - Indian Statistical Institute, 1987 (Box 51)
    - Industrial Ecology, 1991 (Box 24)
    - Information as a Good, 2003 (Box 24)
      Lecture given at "Stiglitz Conference"
    - Information Economics and Policy, 1981-1993 (Box 51)
    - Information Systems Frontiers, 1997-2002 (Box 24)
      Files related to serving on advisory board for journal: Information Systems Frontiers: Emerging Vistas
    - INFORMS (Institute for Operations Research and the Management Sciences), 1994-2013 (Box 24)
    - Innovation Diffusion, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Institute d'Études Politiques des Paris, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Institute d'Etudes Politiques, 1985 (Box 24)
    - Institute for Civil Justice, 1980-1987 (Box 51)
    - Institute for Research on Poverty, 1984-1988 (Box 52)
      Files related to institute at University of Wisconsin - Madison
    - Institutions and Development, 2005 (Box 24)
      Comments given at conference on Institutions and Development
    - Intellectual Properties, 2002 (Box 24)
      Remarks given at FTC/DOJ hearings on competition and intellectual property law at Berkeley
    - International Center for Economic Growth, 2000 (Box 52)
    - International Center for Theoretical Physics, 1998-2006 (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on Scientific Council
    - International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis, 1976-1979 (Box 52)
    - International Panel on Social Progress, 2014 (Box 24)
    - International Reconstruction Bank, 2015 (Box 24)
      Presentation on "Some Fundamentals of Economics: Allocation, Knowledge, and Prices"
    - International Society for Inventory Research, 1982-1994; 2 folders (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on executive committee
    - International Studies Association, 2002 (Box 24)
    - Interpersonal Comparability Conference, 1987 (Box 24)
    - Institute of Medicine (IOM), 1980-1993; 3 folders (Box 51)
      Files related to membership in IOM
    - IOM, 1981-2014 (Box 24)
    - IOM, 2011-2013 (Box 24)
    - IOM: Antimalarial, 2002-2004 (Box 51)
    - IOM: Committee on Environment, 1979-1981 (Box 51)
    - IOM: Election, 1987 (Box 51)
    - IOM: Election, 1988 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Final Draft - Comments, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Financing, 2003 (Box 52)
    - IOM: General Background, 2001-2003 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Global Fund - WHO, 2004-2009; 2 folders (Box 52)
    - IOM: Membership Committee, 1977 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Miscellaneous Info, 2003-2008 (Box 52)
    - IOM: National Academy of Sciences, 1974-1979 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Post-Report, 2005-2007 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Press, 2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: RBM Meeting, 2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Sachs, 2002 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Study Barat Report, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Study Post-report, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Study Pre-report Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 52)
    - IOM: Under 5 Mortality Rates, 2003 (Box 52)
    - Iowa Lecture, 1992 (Box 24)
      Files related to Ida Beam Distinguished Visiting Professorship
    - IPCC (Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change), 1995 (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on Working Group for IPCC
    - IPCC: Review, 1999-2000 (Box 52)
    - IPER (Institute of Professional Education and Research), 2006 (Box 24)
      Documents related to IPER PhD program
    - IPMU (Information Processing and Management of Uncertainty), 1999 (Box 24)
      Files related to Information Processing and Management of Uncertainty conference and follow-up proceedings volume
    - Irvine Advisory, 1985-1988; 4 folders (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on outside advisory committee for School of Social Sciences at UC - Irvine
    - ISIR (International Society for Inventory Research), 1988-2002; 2 folders (Box 24)
      Files related to conference of International Society for Inventory Research
    - Israel, 2014 (Box 24)
    - Israel Conference on Science and Technology, 2011 (Box 24)
    - Israel English Language College, 1987 (Box 52)
    - Israel-Palestine Science, 2004-2009 (Box 52)
      Files related to proposal evaluation
    - ITS-OECD Conference, 1993 (Box 24)
      Program for conference on international environmental policy
    - Jacques Lesourne Conference, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Japan Development Bank Symposium, 2005 (Box 24)
    - Jean-Jacques Laffont life & work, 2001; Video file derived from optical disc; approximately 0.5 GB. (Digital-materials RL00052-SET-0003)
      Includes video of conference in honor of Jean-Jacques Laffont
    - Jerusalem - New Director, 2008 (Box 52)
      Correspondence related to Jerusalem Summer School
    - Jerusalem - School of Economic Theory, 2009 (Box 52)
      Files related to Jerusalem Summer School
    - Jerusalem Institute for Ethics and Economics, 1986-1991 (Box 52)
    - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1986-1992 (Box 24)
    - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1991-1997; 7 folders (Box 24)
    - Jerusalem Summer Workshop, 1998-2014; 17 folders (Box 25)
    - Jewish Community Federation, 1982 (Box 52)
    - Jewish Community Federation - South Peninsula Campaign, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Journal of Complexity, 1985 (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on founding editorial board
    - Journal of Corporate and Industrial History, 1988-1990 (Box 52)
      Files related to serving on scientific committee
    - Journal of Health Economics, 1984 (Box 52)
      Files related to serving as associate editor
    - Journal of Mathematical Economics, 1980-1991 (Box 52)
    - Journal of Risk and Uncertainty, 1987-1993 (Box 52)
    - JPL (Jet Propulsion Laboratory), 1983; 2 folders (Box 53)
      Files related to participation in US Army Innovations Study
    - Kaiser Family Foundation, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Karlin Conference, 2004 (Box 25)
      Files related to conference in honor of Sam Karlin
    - Karlsruhe Seminar, 1988-1990 (Box 25)
    - Kauffman Institute, 2011 (Box 25)
    - Keynesian Workshop, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Keystone Center, 1990-1991 (Box 25)
    - King's College, 1986-1987 (Box 53)
    - Knoer, Elsie - Seminar, 1978 (Box 25)
    - Kochar Education Conference, 2001 (Box 25)
    - Koopmans Lecture, 1993 (Box 25)
      Files related to delivering the Koopmans Lecture titled "Methodological Individualism and Social Knowledge"
    - Korea Development Institute, 1991 (Box 25)
    - Kyoto, Economics and Obligation, 2009 (Box 25)
    - Kyung Hee University, 1984 (Box 25)
    - Laffont Conference, 2005 (Box 25)
      Files related to memorial conference for Jean-Jacques Laffont
    - Lazarfield Lecture, Columbia, 1993 (Box 25)
      Lecture titled "Methodological Individualism: An Adequate Basis for the Social Sciences"
    - Lecture at University of California, Davis, 1979 (Box 25)
      Correspondence around possible lecture at UC-Davis
    - Leverhulme Symposium, 2009 (Box 25)
    - Limits of Economic Rationality, 1989 (Box 25)
      Files related to conference held at the University of Bielefeld
    - Long Term Productivity Trends, 1989 (Box 25)
      Talk given to WEFA Group
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1981-1994 (Box 53)
      Files related to consulting for the foundation
    - MacArthur London, 2001 (Box 25)
    - MacArthur: Economics Initiative, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 53)
      Files related to serving on advisory committee for foundation's Economics Initiative
    - MacArthur: General, 1994-2004 (Box 53)
      Files related to grant-funded project
    - MacArthur: Interaction Inequality, 1996-2000 (Box 53)
      Files related to participating in foundation's Social Interactions and Economic Inequality Network
    - MacArthur: Social Interactions, 2001-2005 (Box 53)
    - MacArthur: Sustainability and Inequality, 1997 (Box 53)
      Files related to meeting sponsored by foundation and Santa Fe Institute
    - Macaulay College, 2010 (Box 25)
      Files related to serving as honorary trustee
    - MAHB (Millennium Alliance for Humanity and the Biosphere), 2013 (Box 25)
      Files related to Millennium Alliance for Humanity and the Biosphere workshop
    - Management Development Program, 1986 (Box 25)
    - Manne General Equilibrium, 1984 (Box 25)
      Files related to workshop at Stanford University hosted by Alan Manne
    - Markets for Innovation, Ownership and Control Conference, 1989 (Box 25)
      Files for conference organized by Gunnar Eliasson
    - Maskin Conference, 2014 (Box 25)
      Files for conference in honor of Eric Maskin
    - Mathematics of Operations Research, 1978-1992 (Box 53)
      Files related to serving as advisory editor
    - Mathematics of Ranking, 2010 (Box 63)
      Files for workshop
    - Mattei Foundation, 1993-2002 (Box 53)
    - Maxwell Lecture, 1992 (Box 25)
      Files related to lecture given at McGill University
    - MERIT (Maastricht Economic Research Institute on Innovation and Technology), 1991-1993 (Box 53)
      Files related to presentation
    - Meritocracy Conference, 1995-2000 (Box 25)
      Files related to conference on meritocracy and proceedings volume Meritocracy and Economic Inequality
    - Mexico Lecture, 1990 (Box 25)
      Lecture on "Transition from Socialism"
    - Michigan/SFI (Santa Fe Institute) Output, 1991 (Box 25)
      Files related to Santa Fe Institute-University of Michigan joint faculty seminar
    - Milan, 1995 (Box 25)
      Files related to seminar at Catholic University of the Sacred Heart in Milan, Italy
    - Milken Institute, 1998 (Box 25)
      Lectures given at Milken Institute
    - Milken Institute, 2007 (Box 53)
      Correspondence related to presentation
    - Miscellaneous Seminar, 1981-1983 (Box 25)
    - MIT Honor, 2000 (Box 25)
      Files related to being named distinguished scholar at 50th anniversary celebration of MIT's School of Humanities and Social Science
    - MIT Visit, 1966 (Box 25)
      Files related to visiting professorship at MIT
    - Mitchell Madison, 1996 (Box 25)
      Files related to keynote address at Mitchel Madison Group annual conference
    - Monash Increasing Returns Conference, 1996 (Box 25)
    - Monash University Visit, 1995 (Box 25)
    - Moscow Trip, 1990 (Box 25)
      Includes hand-written notes on trip to Moscow
    - Moscow Trip, 2012 (Box 25)
      Lecture on "Information as an Economic Commodity"
    - MSRI, 1985-1986 (Box 25)
      Files related to seminar at Mathematical Sciences Research Institute
    - NAACP - Legal Defense Fund, 1993 (Box 53)
    - NAPAP (National Acid Precipitation Assessment Program), 1990 (Box 53)
      Files related to serving on Oversight Review Board
    - NAPAP: Oversight, 1989-1991; 9 folders (Box 53)
    - Naples Institute, 1999 (Box 25)
    - NAS (National Academy of Sciences), 1980-1993 (Box 53)
      Files related to serving as member of the Academy and on the Council
    - NAS, 1987-1988 (Box 53)
      Files related to serving as member of the Academy, on committees, and on the Academy Council
    - NAS: Academy Forum, 1973-1979 (Box 25)
      Files related to National Academy of Sciences forum on nuclear energy
    - NAS: Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 53)
    - NAS: Award Committee on Nuclear War - Estes Award, 1989 (Box 53)
    - NAS: Bowles, 2008-2009 (Box 25)
      Files related to National Academy of Sciences nominations
    - NAS: Budget and Internal Affairs, 1992 (Box 53)
    - NAS: Comments, 1998 (Box 54)
    - NAS: CHR (Committee on Human Rights), 1991-2004; 3 folders (Box 54)
    - NAS: CHR, 1996-2012; 2 folders (Box 25)
      Files related to National Academy of Sciences Committee on Human Rights
    - NAS: Council, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 54)
    - NAS: Environment - TNG, 2000-2002 (Box 54)
    - NAS: General, 1996-2004 (Box 25)
    - NAS: General Advisory Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 54)
    - NAS: Government-University-Industry Roundtable, 1983-1986; 2 folders (Box 54)